Guide to the Oliver F. Atkins photograph collection, 1943-1975
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: 4x5" Negatives, 1947-1956; (9 boxes)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, October 1947 (Box 56, Folder 159)
    Louis B. Meyer, Paul V. McNutt; 5 negatives
  - Never Give a Passenger a Break, February 28, 1948 (Box 56, Folder 160)
    National Airport, Capitol Hill, 1947; 49 negatives
  - Father and Son athletic club, Cleveland Park, Washington, D.C., 1947-1948 (Box 56, Folder 161)
    19 negatives
  - William Rogers, November 1949 (Box 56, Folder 162)
  - Handy Man Goes Banker, November 1, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 163)
    John McCloy, April 1947; 10 negatives
  - Carl Albert, undated (Box 56, Folder 164)
    28 negatives
  - World's Most Glamorous Trash Heap, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 165)
    Kenilworth garbage dump; 31 negatives
  - Government printing office, July 1950 (Box 56, Folder 166)
  - White House bath story, June 1952 (Box 56, Folder 167)
    33 negatives
  - He Drives the Big Brass Crazy, March 1952 (Box 56, Folder 168)
    F. Edward Herbert; 27 negatives
  - He Is Giving Us All a Cleaning, July 1952 (Box 56, Folder 169)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Frank Monaghan; 27 negatives
  - Paleface Pays a Debt, April 1952 (Box 56, Folder 170)
    Bureau of Indian Affairs; 21 negatives
  - David Andrew Pine, July 1952 (Box 56, Folder 171)
    11 negatives
  - That Dizzy Diplomatic Whirl, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 172)
    Embassy of France, Embassy of Spain, Embassy of Mexico; 14 negatives
  - No One Looks Over My Shoulder, March 1952 (Box 56, Folder 173)
    Demolitions Disposal Unit; 21 negatives
  - How The Slovaks Fight The Reds, November 1951 (Box 57, Folder 174)
    Stefan Krajcovic; 8 negatives
  - Gold at The End of Wall Street, August 1952 (Box 57, Folder 175)
    Trinity Church, Gary Edwards; 16 negatives
  - Birth Certificates Census Bureau, March 1952 (Box 57, Folder 176)
  - Spanish Swindle Racket (Adventure for Sale, Price $10,000), August 1952 (Box 57, Folder 177)
    2 negatives
  - The Army's Civilian Brain (ORO), September 1951 (Box 57, Folder 178)
  - India Edwards, undated (Box 57, Folder 179)
    includes Hubert Humphrey, Eugenie Anderson
  - Leo Cullinane, March 1952 (Box 57, Folder 180)
    10 negatives
  - A Veritable Acropolis, September 1952 (Box 57, Folder 181)
    National Gallery of Art; 39 negatives
  - Joseph Kennedy Latin Boys School, 1905 (Box 57, Folder 182)
  - Nobody Loves Clarence, March 25, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 183)
    Clarence Cannon, includes Harry S. Truman; 17 negatives
  - George Allen - When a President Needs Friend, May 5, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    March 1956; 35mm negatives
    Also see Box 49
  - Sonny Lister - Denver, Colorado Heavyweight with a Past, August 13, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    35mm negatives
  - Boss of the Bindman, March 10, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Donald Quarles; 35mm negatives
  - Grudge Fight in Oregon, August 4, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    Wayne Morse; 35mm negatives
  - Clown on Capitol Hill, December 20, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    T. James Tumulty; 35mm negatives
  - Secretary of Things in General (Box 58, Folder 17)
    35mm and 2x2" negatives
  - Headaches of a Hotelkeeper - Part 2 and 3, December 14 and 21, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    Statler Hotel; 35mm negatives
    Also see Box 50
  - What Would You Do with Triplets?, December 29, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Mystery Man of the White House, February 6, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    Robert Cutler; 35mm negatives
  - How to be a Crime Buster, March 19, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    Warren Olney III; 35mm negatives
    Also see Box 51
  - Battle of Giants in Kentucky, September 18, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 48a)
  - Private Life of a Steel Boss, December 6, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - The Truth About General Grow's Moscow Diary, September 27, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - Senator Gore, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 56)
  - Singer's Money Machine, July 7, 1951; July 28, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 58)
    2x2" negatives
  - The Old School Bus Comes Adventuring, July 29, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 62)
    May 1950; 2x2" negatives
  - Baseball's Improbable Imports, August 2, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 67)
    Also see Box 52
  - Elder Benson's Going to Catch It, March 28, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 68)
    Ezra Taft Benson, February 1953; 2x2" negatives
  - Are We Letting Our Children Down?, May 13, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 71)
    April 1950; 2x2" negatives
  - So You Don't Ride the Trains Anymore, December 22, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 76)
  - Candidate Bubbling with Charm - Senator Stuart Symington, July 1, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 77)
    Stuart Symington, June, 1956; 35mm negatives
  - Master of the Pentagon - Robert McNamara, August 5, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 78)
  - Our Propaganda Warriors - Voice of America, March 16, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 80)
  - Stormy New Boss of the Pentagon, July 30, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 86)
    Louis Arthur Johnson, June 1949; 2x2" negatives
    Also see Box 53
  - Smartest Dog in Maryland, November 11, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 95)
  - Hard Boiled Idealist- Senator Paul Douglas, August 6, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 96)
  - Why Birds Need Compasses, October 13, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 97)
  - The Rugged Mr. Dulles, May 28, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 98)
  - We Took the Atom Sub to Sea, April 9, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 99)
  - The Army's Most Hysterical Post, December 18, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 100)
  - The Fighting Half-Pint of Capitol Hill, June 18, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 101)
    Frank P. Graham, includes Kerr Scott, May 1949; 2x2" negatives
  - How Washington's Color Line Looks to me, April 3, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 104)
    February 1954; 2x2" negatives
  - How My Hired Man Handles Me, June 20, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 106)
    Jim Perry, Bud Camp; 35mm negatives
  - Earl Warren's Greatest Moment, July 24, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 109)
    Earl Warren; 35mm negatives
  - That Reminds Me - VP Barkley, April 17, 1954; June 5, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 116)
    Alben William Barkley; 2x2" negatives
  - Secretary of State George Marshall, October 1950 (Box 58, Folder 117)
    Includes Dean Acheson; 2x2" negatives
  - They've Got The Goods on Washington's Cops, September 27, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 124)
  - The Case of The Unexpected Senator, July 31, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 125)
  - Charlotte, North Carolina, June 23, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 126)
    Also see Box 54
  - The President's Day, December 1953 (Box 58, Folder 127)
    Dwight D. Eisenhower; 2x2" negatives
  - First Florist of the Land, September 10, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 135)
    Robert M. Redmond, August 1949; 2x2" negatives
  - We Try to Make It Easy for You, February 21, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 136B)
    George J. Schoeneman; 2x2" negatives
  - Veterans Family Doctor Meets Crisis - Boss Medicine Man, October 4, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 140)
  - They're Just Wild about Boudreau, September 4, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 145)
    Lou Boudreau, August 1948; 2x2" negatives
    Also see Box 55
  - And She Still Likes Movies (Box 58, Folder 147)
  - General McAuliffe Says Nuts to The Atom, July 29, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 151)
  - We Must Have Military Training Now - Secretary of War Patterson, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 152)
  - Washington Five Percenters, August 1949 (Box 58, Folder 154)
    Paul Brindle, Alden H. Waite, Clyde R. Hoey, Herbert Feldman, Harry Vaughn, John F. Maragon; 2x2" Negatives
  - James Forrestal, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 156)
    Also see Box 56
  - Father and Son athletic club, Cleveland Park, Washington, D.C., 1947-1948 (Box 58, Folder 161)
- Series 3: Negatives, Contact Sheets, Slides, 1945-1975; (45 boxes)
  Series 3 contains 35mm negatives, 4x5" negatives, contact sheets, and slides that Atkins created while he worked for the Saturday Evening Post in the 1950s and 1960s as well as some images from work he did during World War II. Prints from these images can be found in Series 1, and there are some copies of negatives that are in Series 4.
  - Subseries 3.1: Chronological, 1961-1968; (9.5 boxes)
    Subseries 3.1 is arranged in chronological order and appears to be largely from Atkins' Washington File, a collection of images he maintained from various assignments. The bulk of the collection documents the administrations of Presidents John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson. There is also significant documentation of events in Washington, D.C., particularly demonstrations and events associated with the Civil Rights Movement.
    - Chronological, January 1961 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, February 1961 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, March 1961 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, April 1961 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, May 1961 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, June 1961 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, July 1961 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, August 1961 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, September 1961 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, November 1961 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Chronological, January 1962 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Chronological, February 1962 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Chronological, March 1962 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Chronological, April 1962 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Chronological, May 1962 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Chronological, June 1962 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Chronological, July 1962 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, August 1962 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, September 1962 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, October 1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, November 1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, January 1963 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, February 1963 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, February 1963 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, May 1963 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, June 1963 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Chronological, July 1963 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Chronological, August 1963 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Chronological, September 1963 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Chronological, October 1963 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, November 1963 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, December 1963 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, January 1964 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, February 1964 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, March 1964 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, April 1964 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, May 1964 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, June 1964 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, July 1964 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, August 1964 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, September 1964 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, October 1964 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, November 1964 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, December 1964 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, January 1965 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, February 1965 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, March 1965 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, April 1965 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, May 1965 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, June 1965 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, July 1965 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, September 1965 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, October 1965 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, November 1965 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, December 1965 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, January 1966 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, February 1966 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, March 1966 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, April 1966 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, May 1966 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, June 1966 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, July 1966 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, August 1966 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, September 1966 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, October 1966 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, November 1966 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, December 1966 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, December 1966 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, January 1967 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, February 1967 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, February 1967 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, March 1967 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, April 1967 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, May 1967 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, June 1967 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, July 1967 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, August 1967 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, October 1967 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, November 1967 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, December 1967 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, January 1968 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, February 1968 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, March 1968 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, April 1968 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, May 1968 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, June 1968 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, July 1968 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, August 1968 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 3.2: Alphabetical, 1945-1975; (34.5 boxes)
    Subseries 3.2 is arranged in alphabetical order. Subjects include Presidents Dwight D. Eisenhower, John F. Kennedy, and Lyndon B. Johnson, along with their cabinet members and families. Other political figures or events include United States Senators and Congressmen, such as Barry Goldwater, J. William Fulbright, and Margaret Chase Smith, and the Democratic and Republican National Conventions from 1956-1968. As in Subseries 1.1, multiple folders titles are based on Saturday Evening Post story titles.
    - Adams, Sherman, 1950s (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Adenauer, Konrad, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Adventures in Expansion Hungarians, June 1958 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Africa, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      (1 of 4)
    - Africa, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      (2 of 4)
    - Africa, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      (3 of 4)
    - Africa, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      (4 of 4)
    - African Queen, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, 1950s (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Allen, George E., 1956, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Alsop, Elizabeth, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Alsop, John, September 1966 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      Connecticut Gubernatorial Campaign
    - Alsop, Joseph, January 1950, December 1964 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      Georgetown House portraits
    - Alsop, Stewart, December 1956 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      Polling
    - Alsop, Stewart, September 1957 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      I Flew Supersonic
    - Alsop, Stewart, October 1960 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      How to Speak French
    - Alsop, Stewart, October 1960, September 1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Alsop, Stewart, January 1961, August 27, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Alsop, Stewart, December 1961 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      Stewart Alsop Family
    - Alsop, Stewart, May 1962 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      How to Write a Magazine Article
    - Alsop, Stewart, July 1962, July 25, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      Polling, Negro poll
    - Alsop, Stewart, July-September 1962 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      Alsop poll "Mood of America"
    - Alsop, Stewart, September 1962 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      John F. Kennedy
    - Alsop, Stewart, 1963-1966 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Alsop, Stewart, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      Alsop poll
    - American Forgotten Flyer, June 1961, August 1964 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      Biplanes
    - Anderson, Robert, January 1959 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Bill, June 1963 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Antique Airplane, May 1960 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      They Make Flying Fun Again
    - Arlington National Cemetery, 1950s (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Armbristen, Trevor, January 1967 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      Trevor Armbristen Family
    - Arthritis, July 12, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Astronauts, February 1961 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Acheson, Dean, October 1962 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Atkins, Oliver, 1960s-1970s (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Atomic Submarine Skipjack, November 1959 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Bagkikian, Ben H., 1966 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Baker, Bobby, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Royal Blue Last Run, April 1958 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Battle, Mark, September 1965 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Battleship North Carolina, October 1961 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Bees, December 1961, June 1962 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Bernstein, Charles, October 1963 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Bicentennial Book, April 10, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Big Business Wants Few Generals, 1950s-1960s (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Big Ear in Lost Valley, November 1969 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Blair, Clay, Jr., March 1957 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Borgstedt Dog at Dog Show, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Brennan, William J., July 1957 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Bronicirik, Ziggy "Red in the White House", March 1964 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Mrs. Paul, Jr., 1967 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Brownell, Herbert, 1952 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, September-October 1961 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Burch, Dean, February 1965 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Burke, May 1952 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      Golf's Banking on Burke
    - Butch Has a New Pair of Arms, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Cambridge, Maryland, September 1963 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Can We Stop Soviet Subs, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      by Sherwood Harris
    - Cancer Research at NIH, April 1964 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Cape Canaveral, Florida, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      Mercury 6 launch
    - Cape Cod[?], 1962 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Carr, Roland, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Case, Clifford, January 1961 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Case for the B-70, March 1960 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      Generals LeMay and White
    - Case for the Republicans, August 1960 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Case of Nervous Syllables, April 1957 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Castro, Fidel, April 1959 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Catto, Henry, July 17, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1950s-1960s (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Chambers, Mrs. Whittaker, August 1964 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Charity Article, July 1960 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Charm School, June 1960 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Charm School, February 1, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - China, 1970s (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - China, 1970s (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Church, Frank, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Clark, Joseph, March 1957 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Clouds, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Record, March 1965 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Connally, John B., Jr. and Richard M. Nixon, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Convention (Democratic), 1956 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Convention (Republican), 1956 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Convention (Republican), 1956 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Convention (Democratic), 1960 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Convention (Democratic), 1960 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Convention (Republican), 1960 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Convention (Republican), 1960 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Convention (Democratic), 1964 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Convention (Democratic), 1964 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Convention (Republican), 1964 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Convention (Republican), 1964 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Convention (Republican), 1964 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Convention (Democratic), 1968 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Convention (Republican), 1968 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Corruption in Arkansas, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Country Gentleman, September 8, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Crown, Henry, February 1965 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Cuba Assignment, May 1959 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Cuba Assignment, May 1959 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Cuneo, Sandra, June 1966 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - D.C. Transit Hearings, 1950s (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - D-Day Series, January 1959 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Dancers, 1940s (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Deakin, Phil, December 1959 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Defense and Military Personalities, 1950s (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Defense Contracts, June 1963 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - de Gaulle, Charles, April 1960 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Personalities, 1950s (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Personalities, 1950s (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Demonstrations, October 1967 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Dickerson, Nancy, October 1964 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Diplomatic Whirl, April 1957 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Dirksen, Everett, March 1968 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Dodd, Thomas, March 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Domestic Scene with Family, 1950s (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Don't Sell France Short, October 1957 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Down Range, February 1957 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Down Range, February 1957 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Douglas, Paul H., 1966 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Drummond, Roscoe, January 1963 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Dulles, Allen, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Dulles, John Foster, July 1958 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Dunlap, Jack E., November 1963 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Dunning, Judson, August 1960 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Egypt Assignment, March 1963 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Egypt Assignment, March 1963 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 77, Folder 1)
      color slides
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower, Julie Nixon, 1969-1974 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1960s (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Elk on Military Reservation in Richmond, Virginia, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Estes, Billie Sol, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Evans, Rowland, June 1961, August 1964 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - F-111, November 1966 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax City, Virginia, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax High School Band, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Fairfax Library dedication, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax National Bank, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Fairfax Volunteer Fire Department, April 1963 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Goldfine, Bernard, July 1958 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Farmers from Georgia visit Soviet farms, May 1962 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - FBI and J. Edgar Hoover, July 1965 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Federal Reserve System Story, 1950s (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Fenwick, Millicent, March 26, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Fish Food Story, October 1963 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Travel, December 1960-January 1961 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Freeway at Capitol, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Frohman, I. G., 1959 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Fruehauf story, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Fulbright, J. William, February 17, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Galbraith, Kenneth, November 1959 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Gates, Thomas, March 1960 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Gavin, James M., 1961 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      Includes John F. Kennedy
    - Gettysburg, Pennsylvania, June 1959 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Gilbert, Bill, July 1967 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - General Lee, the Cunnel, and Me, July 1957 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Glennan, T. Keith, February 1959 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Godfrey, Arthur, 1955 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Goldberg, Arthur, July 26, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Goldberg, Arthur, March 1961 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Goldfine hearings, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      Bernard Goldfine
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1958-1964 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Gordan, Ginanetta, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Green, Wallace, October 1964 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Griffin, Robert, January 1966 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Gross, H. R., June 1964 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Ground Effect Machines, September 1961 (Box 79, Folder 8)